safeyoutube.net 2019-01-06

# Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

In general, you can visit and browse safeYouTube.tv anonymously without revealing any personal information about yourself. The only information that we gather during your general browsing can be information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the websites that referred you to us, the pages you visit on our website, and the dates/times of those visits. All of these information will not specifically identify you and will be used internally only for web site traffic analysis.

We collect personal information from you just when you register on our site or make a donation. When making a donation or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or credit card information. This information is collected only with your knowledge and permission. 

## What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
1) to personalize your experience, as your information helps us respond to your individual needs in a better way.  
2) to improve our website as we continually strive to improve our website services based on the information, feedback and donations we receive from you.  
3) to improve customer service as your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
4) to send periodic emails.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. And there will always be an unsubscribe link included in each email. In all cases, your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other third party for any reason whatsoever. Your privacy on the internet is of utmost importance to us. 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of technologies and security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

## Third party links 

Our website may contain links to other websites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. 

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our website may make any changes to their information. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

safeYouTube.net reserves the right to amend this privacy policy and if we decide, at any time, to change it, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 10/4/2015

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please Contact Us
